Hey, Caleb Banks. Welcome to Minnesota.
I'm your announcer, Paul Allen. I call
the games on radio. That's former
linebacker Ben Leber back there. We are
so excited to see you wear purple. Holy
cow, 6-6, 320 and change. Man, the
Minnesota Vikings drafted a game changer
in Caleb Banks to join an already good
defense, one of the better defenses in
the NFL last year. So, excellent
excellent pick. Best of luck to you,
Caleb Banks. Can't wait to meet you.
Thing to keep in mind with this pick is
that
had Caleb Banks not had the foot injury
he's going off his 2024 tape. He would
have been one of the top five picks in
the draft. This kid has potential to be
an All-Pro year after year after year to
dominate the inside of offensive lines
for years to come. And under Brian
Flores
and that's the other part of it that
just blows my mind is versatility. Caleb
Banks is such a great athlete. In high
school he played he played tight end, he
played quarterback, he played wide
receiver before just outgrowing all
those positions and then moving to
defensive line.
The versatility is there, the
athleticism is there, the size is
definitely there. It's just one
question. And you get that figured out,
Caleb Banks could be
one of the biggest selections that the
Vikings have made in a very very long
time. I'm so excited to see this kid on
the turf come this summer.
We say it all the time, you build the
team in the trenches, offensive line and
defensive line. So, here we were
thinking this whole time that we had to
fill the safety position. But then a guy
like Caleb Banks, who we just heard head
coach Kevin O'Connell talk about how if
he was not injured last year, this is a
top 10 talent and a top 10 selection in
this draft. So, we got tremendous value
at 18. We got a game wrecker at 18 as
long as he stays healthy. So, I love the
fact that we're building this team once
again through the trenches. NFC North
offensive lines, you're on the lookout.